
  Usage
    $ svelte-check [options]

  Options
    --workspace              Path to your workspace. All subdirectories except node_modules and those listed in `--ignore` are checked. Defaults to current working directory.
    --output                 What output format to use. Options are human, human-verbose, machine, machine-verbose.  (default human-verbose)
    --watch                  Will not exit after one pass but keep watching files for changes and rerun diagnostics  (default false)
    --preserveWatchOutput    Do not clear the screen in watch mode  (default false)
    --tsconfig               Pass a path to a tsconfig or jsconfig file. The path can be relative to the workspace path or absolute. Doing this means that only files matched by the files/include/exclude pattern of the config file are diagnosed. It also means that errors from TypeScript and JavaScript files are reported. When not given, searches for the next upper tsconfig/jsconfig in the workspace path.
    --no-tsconfig            Use this if you only want to check the Svelte files found in the current directory and below and ignore any JS/TS files (they will not be type-checked)  (default false)
    --ignore                 Only has an effect when using `--no-tsconfig` option. Files/folders to ignore - relative to workspace root, comma-separated, inside quotes. Example: `--ignore "dist,build"`
    --fail-on-warnings       Will also exit with error code when there are warnings  (default false)
    --compiler-warnings      A list of Svelte compiler warning codes. Each entry defines whether that warning should be ignored or treated as an error. Warnings are comma-separated, between warning code and error level is a colon; all inside quotes. Example: `--compiler-warnings "css-unused-selector:ignore,unused-export-let:error"`
    --diagnostic-sources     A list of diagnostic sources which should run diagnostics on your code. Possible values are `js` (includes TS), `svelte`, `css`. Comma-separated, inside quotes. By default all are active. Example: `--diagnostic-sources "js,svelte"`
    --threshold              Filters the diagnostics to display. `error` will output only errors while `warning` will output warnings and errors.  (default warning)
    --color                  Force enabling of color output  (default false)
    --no-color               Force disabling of color output  (default false)
    -v, --version            Displays current version
    -h, --help               Displays this message

